{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","address":"3975 Conner Ave","zipcode":"48215","owner":"ECS Partnership","licenseNumber":"062429","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"6/6/2017","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E6100000A4ADA223FFBD54C0201EDB0227314540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44764","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","inspectionDate":"2019-01-04T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[]},{"inspectionid":"44506","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","inspectionDate":"2018-12-10T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Complaint","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44506","inspectionDate":"12/10/2018","inspectionType":"Complaint","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"FRONT COUNTER/AREA","subLocation":"On the Floor","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"44089","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","inspectionDate":"2018-11-13T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44089","inspectionDate":"11/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Single-service/single-use article(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"On the floor Single service items","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store at least 6 inches above the floor."},{"inspectionid":"44089","inspectionDate":"11/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Under the Fryer(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"44089","inspectionDate":"11/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"44089","inspectionDate":"11/13/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"With handle in product","location":"FOOD PREP.","subLocation":"Inside the Ice machine","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-13T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store with handle extended out of product."}]},{"inspectionid":"40861","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","inspectionDate":"2017-10-31T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"7","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"7","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40861","inspectionDate":"10/31/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cooler (small)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"40861","inspectionDate":"10/31/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Inside the Walk-in freezer","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"40861","inspectionDate":"10/31/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"At the Cooler (small)","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Store below 41 degrees F."},{"inspectionid":"40861","inspectionDate":"10/31/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Drainage system","subItem":"drain lines","problemDescription":"Not constructed, designed, installed according to law","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Floor drain(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove and replace to be in compliance with law."},{"inspectionid":"40861","inspectionDate":"10/31/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Electrical outlet","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"40861","inspectionDate":"10/31/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"6-302.11","violationDescription":"A supply of toilet tissue shall be available at each toilet.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Toilet paper","subItem":"at toilet in restroom employee","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Missing Toilet paper","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"40861","inspectionDate":"10/31/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at 30 inches above the floor","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"40861","inspectionDate":"10/31/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Broken","subProblem":"","location":"DRIVE-THRU WINDOW","subLocation":"At the Handsink","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"40861","inspectionDate":"10/31/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (MEN'S PUBLIC)","subLocation":"At the Toilet","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"40861","inspectionDate":"10/31/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"3-304.12","violationDescription":"During pauses in FOOD preparation or dispensing, UTENSILS shall be stored:\r\n(A) In the FOOD with their handles above the top of the FOOD and the container;\r\n(B) In FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS with their handles above the      top of the FOOD within containers or EQUIPMENT that can be closed, such as      bins of sugar, flour, or cinnamon;\r\n(C) On a clean portion of the FOOD preparation table or cooking EQUIPMENT\r\n(D)  In running water, such as dipper well.\r\n(E)  In a clean, protected location if the UTENSILS, such as ice scoops, are   used only with a FOOD that is not POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS; or\r\n(F)  In a container of water maintained at a temperature of at least 135° F.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Dispensing utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Improperly stored","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Ice scoop","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Relocate."}]},{"inspectionid":"36896","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","inspectionDate":"2016-10-25T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"1","pfcount":"0","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"1","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"1","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36896","inspectionDate":"10/25/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"2646","name":"McDonald's #25135","violationCode":"5-202.13","violationDescription":"An air gap between the water supply inlet and the flood level rim of the PLUMBING FIXTURE, EQUIPMENT, or nonFOOD EQUIPMENT shall be at least twice the diameter of the water supply inlet and may not be less than 1 inch. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Air gap","subItem":"between supply line and flood rim of plumbing fixture","problemDescription":"Less than twice the diameter of supply line","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Over head spray unit ","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-11-04T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide air gap that is twice the diameter of the drain line and no less than 1 inch."}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"2646"}}